const startButton = document.querySelector("startbtn");
const button1 = document.querySelector("btn-1")
const button2 = document.querySelector("btn-2")
const button3 = document.querySelector("btn-3")
const button4 = document.querySelector("btn-4")


//move to pg 1
// startButton.addeventListener('click', startGame);
// function startGame() {
//   console.log("game started");
// }

// for (let i = 0; index < questions.length; index++) {
//   const element = array[index];
  
// }

// let questions = [
//   {
//     question: "What was the original model name for the Porsche 911?",
//     options: [
//       "900",
//       "901",
//       "912",
//       "beetle"
//     ]
//     answer: 1
//   }

//   {
//     question: "In what year did the compoany make its first vehicle?",
//     options: [
//       "1936",
//       "1955",
//       "1944",
//       "1948"
//     ]
//     answer: 3
//   }

//   {
//     question: "Porsche is famous at the LeMans 24 hour endurance race.  How many victories do they have?",
//     options: [
//       "8",
//       "28",
//       "4",
//       "19"
//     ]
//     answer: 3
//   }

//   {
//     question: "What type of engine does the Porsche 911 have?",
//     options: [
//       "V8",
//       "V12",
//       "Flat 6",
//       "4 cylinder"
//     ]
//     answer: 2
//   }

//   {
//     question: "Porsche is the worlds largest manufacturer of What?",
//     options: [
//       "Flat 6 Engines",
//       "Racecars",
//       "SUVs",
//       "Sportscars"
//     ]
//     answer: 1
//   }

//   {
//     question: "What country is Porsche from?",
//     options: [
//       "Germany",
//       "France",
//       "Italy",
//       "USA"
//     ]
//     answer: 0
//   }

//   {
//     question: "What is the top of the line 911 model name?",
//     options: [
//       "Carrera 4S",
//       "911 Turbo",
//       "GT2 RS",
//       "911 Turbo S"
//     ]
//     answer: 2
//   }

//   {
//     question: "What company owns Porsche?",
//     options: [
//       "Volkswagen",
//       "Ferrari",
//       "Ford",
//       "Mercedes"
//     ]
//     answer: 0
//   }

//   {
//     question: "What animal is on the Porsche Crest?",
//     options: [
//       "Eagle",
//       "Lion",
//       "Prancing Horse",
//       "Bat"
//     ]
//     answer: 2
//   }

//   {
//     question: "What is the name of Porsche's first SUV?",
//     options: [
//       "Macan",
//       "Cayenne",
//       "Taycan",
//       "Panamera"
//     ]
//     answer: 1
//   }
// ]

//Event listener to change button color on click
button1.addEventListener("click", () => {
  button1.style.backgroundColor = "yellow";
  button1.style.color = "white";
  console.log("clicked");
})

button2.addEventListener("click", () => {
  button1.style.backgroundColor = "yellow";
})

button3.addEventListener("click", () => {
  button1.style.backgroundColor = "yellow";
})

button4.addEventListener("click", () => {
  button1.style.backgroundColor = "yellow";
})

function nextQuestion() {


}

function answerSelect() {


}